Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Motion Pictures and Audiorecordings Documenting Football
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Football game films, 1975-1976; Accession 2007-A-086
  - Drive, 1975; 1 (Box 134)
  - 526-324, 1975; 1 (Box 135)
  - 64, 1975; 1 (Box 136)
  - Brown
    - Offense, 1976; 2 (Box 137–138)
    - Defense, 1976; 2 (Box 139–140)
    - Sequential (color), 1976; 4 (Box 141–144)
  - UConn, 1976; 4 (Box 145–148)
  - Lehigh, 1976; 4 (Box 149–152)
  - Dartmouth
    - Sequential, 1976; 4 (Box 153–156)
    - Sequential (color), 1976; 4 (Box 157–160)
  - Columbia
    - Sequential, 1976; 4 (Box 161–164)
    - Sequential (color), 1976; 4 (Box 165–168)
  - Penn
    - Sequential, 1976; 4 (Box 169–172)
    - Sequential (color), 1976; 4 (Box 173–176)
  - Cornell
    - Sequential, 1976; 4 (Box 177–180)
    - Sequential (color), 1976; 4 (Box 181–184)
  - Princeton
    - Sequential, 1976; 4 (Box 185–188)
    - Sequential (color), 1976; 4 (Box 189–192)
  - Harvard
    - Defense, 1976; 4 (Box 193–196)
  - Season Highlights, 1976; 1 (Box 197)
  - Freshmen vs. Army, 1976; 4 (Box 198–201)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1976; 4 (Box 202–205)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1976; 4 (Box 206–209)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1976; 4 (Box 210–213)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1976; 4 (Box 214–217)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1976; 4 (Box 218–221)
  - Freshmen
    - 1976 Sep 11, 1 (Box 222)
    - 1976 Sep 18, 1 (Box 223)
    - 1976 Sep 25, 1 (Box 224)
- Football game films, 1977-1978; Accession 2007-A-097
  - Brown, 1977; 4 (Box 1–4)
  - UConn, 1977; 4 (Box 5–8)
  - Miami, 1977; 4 (Box 9–12)
  - Dartmouth, 1977; 4 (Box 13–16)
  - Columbia, 1977; 4 (Box 17–20)
  - Penn, 1977; 4 (Box 21–24)
    - Use copy for boxes 21-24, 1 (Box 21U)
  - Cornell, 1977; 4 (Box 25–28)
  - Princeton, 1977; 4 (Box 29–32)
  - Harvard, 1977; 4 (Box 33–36)
    - Use copy for boxes 33-36, 1 (Box 33U)
  - C.W. Post, 1977; 4 (Box 37–40)
  - Season highlights, 1977; 1 (Box 41)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 41U)
  - Freshmen vs. SCSU, 1977; 3 (Box 42–44)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1977; 4 (Box 45–48)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1977; 4 (Box 49–52)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1977; 4 (Box 53–56)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1977; 4 (Box 57–60)
  - Freshmen vs. Army, 1977; 4 (Box 61–64)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1977; 4 (Box 65–68)
  - Freshmen
    - 1977 Sep 10, 2 (Box 69–70)
    - 1977 Sep 17, 2 (Box 71–72)
  - Brown, 1978; 4 (Box 73–76)
    - Use copy for boxes 73-76, 1 (Box 73U)
  - UConn, 1978; 4 (Box 77–80)
  - Rutgers, 1978; 4 (Box 81–84)
  - Dartmouth, 1978; 4 (Box 85–88)
    - Use copy for boxes 85-88, 1 (Box 85U)
  - Columbia, 1978; 4 (Box 89–92)
  - Penn, 1978; 4 (Box 93–96)
  - Cornell, 1978; 4 (Box 97–100)
    - Use copy for boxes 97-100, 1 (Box 97U)
  - Princeton, 1978; 4 (Box 101–104)
  - Harvard, 1978; 3 (Box 105–107)
    - Use copy for boxes 105-107, 1 (Box 105U)
  - C.W. Post, 1978; 3 (Box 108–110)
  - Season highlights, 1978; 1 (Box 111)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 111U)
  - JV vs. Harvard, 1978; 4 (Box 112–115)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1978; 4 (Box 116–119)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1978; 4 (Box 120–123)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1978; 4 (Box 124–127)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1978; 4 (Box 128–131)
  - Freshmen vs. Army, 1978; 4 (Box 132–135)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1978; 4 (Box 136–139)
- Football game films, 1979-1980; Accession 2007-A-133
  - Brown, 1979; 4 (Box 1–4)
    - Use copy for boxes 1-4, 1 (Box 1U)
  - UConn, 1979; 4 (Box 5–8)
  - Colgate, 1979; 4 (Box 9–12)
  - Dartmouth, 1979; 4 (Box 13–16)
  - Columbia, 1979; 4 (Box 17–20)
  - Penn, 1979; 4 (Box 21–24)
    - Use copy for boxes 21-24, 1 (Box 21U)
  - Cornell, 1979; 4 (Box 25–28)
    - Use copy for boxes 25-28, 1 (Box 25U)
  - Princeton, 1979; 4 (Box 29–32)
    - Use copy for boxes 29-32, 1 (Box 29U)
  - Harvard, 1979; 4 (Box 33–36)
    - Use copy for boxes 33-36, 1 (Box 33U)
  - Boston University
    - Defense, 1979; 2 (Box 37–38)
    - Offense, 1979; 1 (Box 39)
  - Season highlights/Ivy League Champs, 1979; 1 (Box 40)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 40U)
  - JV, 1979 October 11; 2 (Box 41–42)
  - JV vs. Freshmen, 1979; 1 (Box 43)
  - Freshmen, 1979 September 15; 1 (Box 44)
  - Freshmen vs. Alamo, 1979 October 22; 1 (Box 45)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1979; 2 (Box 46–47)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1979; 4 (Box 48–51)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1979; 4 (Box 52–55)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1979; 4 (Box 56–59)
  - Freshmen vs. Army, 1979; 3 (Box 60–62)
  - Brown, 1980; 3 (Box 63–65)
  - Air Force, 1980; 4 (Box 66–69)
  - Boston College, 1980; 4 (Box 70–72)
  - Columbia, 1980; 4 (Box 73–76)
  - Penn, 1980; 4 (Box 77–80)
  - Dartmouth, 1980; 4 (Box 81–84)
  - Cornell, 1980; 4 (Box 85–88)
  - Princeton, 1980; 4 (Box 89–92)
  - Harvard, 1980; 4 (Box 93–96)
  - Season Highlights, 1980; 1 (Box 97)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 97U)
  - JV vs. Milford, 1980; 3 (Box 98–100)
  - JV vs. UNNH, 1980; 2 (Box 101–102)
  - JV vs. Princeton, 1980; 4 (Box 103–106)
  - Freshmen vs. Army, 1980; 4 (Box 107–110)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1980; 3 (Box 111–113)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1980; 4 (Box 114–117)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1980; 4 (Box 118–121)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1980; 4 (Box 122–124)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1980; 4 (Box 125–128)
- Football game films, 1981-1982; Accession 2007-A-144
  - Brown, 1981; 4 (Box 1–4)
  - UConn, 1981; 4 (Box 5–8)
  - Navy, 1981; 4 (Box 9–12)
    - Use copy for boxes 9-12, 1 (Box 9U)
  - Holy Cross, 1981; 4 (Box 13–16)
  - Columbia, 1981; 4 (Box 17–20)
  - Princeton, 1981; 4 (Box 21–24)
  - Penn, 1981; 4 (Box 25–28)
  - Cornell, 1981; 4 (Box 29–32)
  - Princeton, 1981; 4 (Box 33–36)
    - Use copy for boxes 33-36, 1 (Box 33U)
  - Harvard, 1981; 4 (Box 37–40)
  - Season highlights, 1981; 1 (Box 41)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 41U)
  - New Hampshire, 1981; 4 (Box 42–45)
  - JV vs. UNH, 1981; 4 (Box 46–49)
  - JV vs. Harvard, 1981; 4 (Box 50–52, Box 132)
  - Freshmen, 1981 September 5; 2 (Box 53–54)
  - Freshmen vs. Army, 1981; 4 (Box 55–58)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1981; 4 (Box 59–62)
  - Brown, 1982; 4 (Box 63–66)
  - UConn, 1982; 4 (Box 67–70)
  - Holy Cross, 1982; 4 (Box 71–74)
  - Boston University, 1982; 4 (Box 75–78)
  - Columbia, 1982; 4 (Box 79–82)
  - Penn, 1982; 4 (Box 83–86)
  - Dartmouth, 1982; 4 (Box 87–90)
  - Cornell, 1982; 4 (Box 91–94)
  - Princeton, 1982; 4 (Box 95–98)
  - Harvard, 1982; 4 (Box 99–102)
  - Season Highlights, 1982; 1 (Box 103)
  - JV vs. Princeton, 1982; 3 (Box 104–106)
  - JV vs. SCSU, 1982; 3 (Box 107–109)
  - JV vs. New Haven, 1982; 3 (Box 110–112)
  - JV vs. Freshmen, 1982; 1 (Box 113)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton
    - Defense, 1982; 2 (Box 114–115)
    - Offense, 1982; 2 (Box 116–117)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1982; 4 (Box 118–121)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1982; 4 (Box 122–125)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1982; 2 (Box 126–127)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia
    - Defense, 1982; 2 (Box 128–129)
    - Offense, 1982; 2 (Box 130–131)
- Football game films, 1983-1984; Accession 2007-A-151
  - Brown, 1983; 4 (Box 1–4)
  - UConn, 1983; 4 (Box 5–8)
  - William and Mary, 1983; 4 (Box 9–12)
  - Boston College, 1983; 4 (Box 13–16)
    - Use copy for boxes 13-16, 1 (Box 13U)
  - Penn, 1983; 4 (Box 17–20)
    - Use copy for boxes 17-20, 1 (Box 17U)
  - Columbia, 1983; 3 (Box 21–23)
    - Use copy for boxes 21-23, 1 (Box 21U)
  - Dartmouth, 1983; 4 (Box 24–27)
  - Cornell, 1983; 4 (Box 28–31)
  - Princeton, 1983; 4 (Box 32–35)
  - Harvard, 1983 November 19; 4 (Box 36–39)
    - Use copy, 1
  - Harvard, the 100th game, 1983 November 19; 1 (Box 40)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 40U)
  - Harvard, 1983 November 19; 1 (Box 162)
    Ivy Network, commercially-produced.
  - New Hampshire, 1983; 3 (Box 41–43)
  - Season highlights, 1983; 1 (Box 44)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 44U)
  - JV vs. Central Connecticut, 1983; 2 (Box 45–46)
  - JV vs. Army, 1983; 3 (Box 47–49)
  - JV vs. Milford, 1983; 4 (Box 50–53)
  - JV vs. Maine, 1983; 4 (Box 54–57)
  - JV vs. Harvard, 1983; 4 (Box 58–61)
  - JV vs. Freshmen
    - 1983 September 19, 4 (Box 62–65)
    - 1983 October 3, 1 (Box 66)
    - 1983 November 7, 2 (Box 67–68)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1983; 3 (Box 69–71)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1983; 3 (Box 72–74)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1983; 4 (Box 75–78)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1983; 4 (Box 79–82)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1983; 4 (Box 83–86)
  - Brown, 1984; 4 (Box 87–90)
  - UConn, 1984; 4 (Box 91–94)
  - Morgan State, 1984; 4 (Box 95–98)
  - Dartmouth, 1984; 4 (Box 99–102)
  - Columbia, 1984; 4 (Box 103–106)
  - Penn, 1984 October 27; 4 (Box 107–110)
    - Use copy for boxes 107-110, 1 (Box 107U)
  - Penn, 1984 October 27; 3 (Box 159–161)
  - Cornell, 1984; 4 (Box 111–114)
  - Princeton, 1984; 4 (Box 115–118)
  - Harvard, 1984; 4 (Box 119–122)
    - Use copy for boxes 119-122, 1 (Box 119U1)
    - Use copy for boxes 119-122, 1 (Box 119U2)
  - SCSU, 1984; 4 (Box 123–126)
  - Season highlights, 1984; 1 (Box 127)
  - JV vs. New Haven
    - 1984 Sep 24, 4 (Box 128–131)
    - 1984 Nov 5, 4 (Box 132–135)
  - JV vs. CCSC
    - 1984 September 8, 2 (Box 136–138)
    - 1984 October 15, 4 (Box 139–142)
  - JV vs. Harvard, 1984; 2 (Box 143–144)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1984; 2 (Box 145–146)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1984; 4 (Box 147–150)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1984; 4 (Box 151–154)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1984; 4 (Box 155–158)
- Football game films, 1985-1986; Accession 2007-A-173
  - Brown, 1985; 4 (Box 1–4)
  - Army, 1985; 4 (Box 5–8)
  - Holy Cross, 1985; 4 (Box 9–12)
  - Columbia, 1985; 4 (Box 13–16)
  - Penn, 1985; 4 (Box 17–20)
  - Dartmouth, 1985; 4 (Box 21–24)
  - Cornell, 1985; 4 (Box 25–28)
  - Princeton, 1985; 4 (Box 29–32)
    - Use copy for boxes 29-32, 1 (Box 29U)
  - Harvard, 1985; 4 (Box 33–36)
    - Use copy for boxes 33-36, 1 (Box 33U–34U)
  - Season highlights, 1985; 1 (Box 37)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 37U)
  - JV vs. Milford, 1985; 4 (Box 38–41)
  - JV vs. SCSU, 1985; 3 (Box 42–44)
  - JV vs. UNH, 1985; 2 (Box 45–46)
  - JV vs. Harvard, 1985; 4 (Box 47–50)
  - JV vs. Central Connecticut, 1985; 3 (Box 51–53)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1985; 3 (Box 54–56)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1985; 2 (Box 57–58)
  - Freshmen vs. Army, 1985; 4 (Box 59–62)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1985; 4 (Box 63–66)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1985; 4 (Box 67–70)
  - Brown, 1986; 4 (Box 71–74)
    - Use copy for boxes 71-74, 1 (Box 71U)
  - UConn, 1986; 4 (Box 75–78)
    - Use copy for boxes 75-78, 1 (Box 75U)
  - Army, 1986; 4 (Box 79–82)
  - Colgate, 1986; 4 (Box 83–86)
  - Columbia, 1986; 2 (Box 87–88)
  - CCSC, 1986; 4 (Box 89–92)
  - Penn, 1986; 4 (Box 93–96)
  - Dartmouth, 1986; 4 (Box 97–100)
  - Cornell, 1986; 4 (Box 101–104)
  - Princeton, 1986; 4 (Box 105–108)
  - Harvard, 1986; 4 (Box 109–112)
    - Use copy for boxes 109-112, 1 (Box 109U)
  - Season highlights, 1986; 1 (Box 113)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 113U)
  - JV vs. Milford Academy, 1986; 2 (Box 114–115)
  - JV vs. UNH, 1986; 3 (Box 116–118)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1986; 3 (Box 119–121)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1986; 2 (Box 122–123)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1986; 3 (Box 124–126)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1986; 2 (Box 127–128)
  - Freshmen vs. Army, 1986; 2 (Box 129–130)
- Football game films, 1987-1988; Accession 2007-A-181
  - Brown, 1987; 4 (Box 1–4)
  - UConn, 1987; 4 (Box 5–8)
  - Hawaii, 1987; 4 (Box 9–12)
  - William and Mary, 1987; 4 (Box 13–16)
  - Columbia, 1987; 4 (Box 17–20)
  - Penn, 1987; 4 (Box 21–24)
  - Dartmouth, 1987; 4 (Box 25–28)
  - Cornell, 1987; 4 (Box 29–32)
  - Princeton, 1987; 4 (Box 131–134)
    - Use copy for boxes 131-134, 1 (Box 131U)
  - Harvard, 1987; 4 (Box 33–36)
  - Villanova, 1987; 3 (Box 37–39)
  - Team tour (Hawaii), 1987; 2 (Box 135–136)
  - JV vs. Harvard, 1987; 4 (Box 40–43)
  - JV vs. Milford Academy, 1987; 4 (Box 44–47)
  - JV vs. Navy Prep, 1987; 4 (Box 48–51)
  - Freshmen vs. Army, 1987; 4 (Box 52–55)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1987; 4 (Box 56–59)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1987; 4 (Box 60–63)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1987; 4 (Box 64–67)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1987; 4 (Box 68–71)
  - Season highlights, 1987; 1 (Box 72)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 72U)
  - Brown, 1988; 4 (Box 73–76)
  - UConn, 1988; 4 (Box 77–80)
  - Navy, 1988; 4 (Box 81–84)
  - Army, 1988; 2 (Box 85–86)
  - Columbia, 1988; 4 (Box 87–90)
  - Penn, 1988; 4 (Box 91–94)
  - Dartmouth, 1988; 4 (Box 95–98)
  - Cornell, 1988; 4 (Box 99–102)
  - Princeton, 1988; 4 (Box 103–106)
  - Harvard, 1988; 4 (Box 107–110)
    - Use copy for boxes 107-110, 2 (Box 107U–108U)
  - Season highlights, 1988; 1 (Box 111)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 111U)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1988; 4 (Box 112–115)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1988; 4 (Box 116–119)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1988; 2 (Box 120–121)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1988; 2 (Box 122–123)
  - JV vs. UNH, 1988; 3 (Box 124–126)
  - JV vs. Harvard, 1988; 4 (Box 127–130)
- Football game films, 1989-1990; Accession 2007-A-201
  - Brown, 1989; 4 (Box 1–4)
  - Lehigh, 1989; 3 (Box 5–7)
  - UConn, 1989; 4 (Box 8–11)
  - Colgate, 1989; 4 (Box 12–15)
  - Dartmouth, 1989; 4 (Box 16–19)
  - Columbia, 1989; 4 (Box 20–23)
  - Penn, 1989; 4 (Box 24–27)
  - Cornell, 1989; 4 (Box 28–31)
  - Princeton, 1989; 4 (Box 114–117)
  - Harvard, 1989; 4 (Box 32–35)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1989; 1 (Box 36)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1989; 1 (Box 37)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1989; 3 (Box 38–40)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1989; 4 (Box 41–44)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1989; 3 (Box 45–47)
  - JV vs. UNH, 1989; 4 (Box 48–51)
  - JV vs. SCSU, 1989; 2 (Box 52–53)
  - Brown, 1990; 4 (Box 54–57)
  - Lafayette, 1990; 4 (Box 58–61)
    - Use copy for boxes 58-61, 1 (Box 58U)
  - UConn, 1990; 4 (Box 62–65)
    - Use copy for boxes 62-65, 1 (Box 62U)
  - Colgate, 1990; 4 (Box 66–69)
    - Use copy for boxes 66-69, 1 (Box 66U)
  - Dartmouth, 1990; 4 (Box 70–73)
  - Columbia, 1990; 4 (Box 74–77)
  - Penn, 1990; 4 (Box 78–81)
  - Cornell, 1990; 4 (Box 82–85)
    - Use copy for boxes 82-85, 1 (Box 82U)
  - Princeton, 1990; 4 (Box 86–89)
  - Harvard, 1990; 4 (Box 90–93)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1990; 4 (Box 94–97)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1990; 4 (Box 98–101)
  - Freshmen vs. Penn, 1990; 3 (Box 102–104)
    - Use copy for boxes 102-104, 1 (Box 102U)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1990; 3 (Box 105–108)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1990; 1 (Box 109)
  - JV vs. SCSU, 1990; 4 (Box 110–113)
- Football films, 1935-1971; Accession 2008-A-051
  - Highlights, 1935-1937; 1 (Box 1)
  - NCAA football, 1951; 1 (Box 2)
  - Pay the price, make it hurt, 1971; 1 (Box 3)
  - History of football at Yale
    - Part 1: Beginning to 1913, 1 (Box 4)
    - Part 2: 1913-1927, 1 (Box 5)
    - Part 3: From Booth to Frank, 1929-1933, 1 (Box 6)
    - Part 4: The Modern Era, 1 (Box 7)
    - Part 5: The tenth decade, 1 (Box 8)
  - Football history, 1 (Box 9)
  - The Albie Booth Story, 1 (Box 10)
  - Yale football - Howard Cosell, 1 (Box 11)
- Yale-Army football game film, 1930; Accession 2013-A-082
  - Yale-Army football game film, 1930; 1 (Box 1)
    Reel also contains film of the Yale-Harvard boat race, probably spring 1930 or 1931.